clearbit.com 2018-07-22

# Clearbit

### Want to control your data and privacy settings?

Clearbit allows you to claim your profile, edit it, and hide or disclose data in your profile.

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 28, 2018.

### Our Policy

APIHub, Inc. (“Clearbit,” “we”, “us” or “our”) developed our services to help you gain valuable business intelligence. We understand that privacy is important to both our online visitors and registered users. We respect your privacy and will take reasonable steps to protect your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Clearbit participates in the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield frameworks. Our Privacy Shield Policy, the terms of which are incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy, can be found [here](https://clearbit.com/privacyshield).

This Privacy Policy will help you understand the following:

  * What does this Privacy Policy apply to?
  * Information collection and use
  * Sharing and disclosure of information
  * Choice and opt-out
  * Protection of information
  * Changes and notifications
  * Jurisdictional issues
  * Access to information; Contact us

In the event of any inconsistency between our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Service prevail.

#### 1\. What does this Privacy Policy apply to?

Clearbit is located at 90 Sheridan St., San Francisco, California, 94103. This Privacy Policy applies to the clearbit.com website, including all subpages and successor pages (collectively referred to as the “Site”), and also applies to all software and services that we offer, including services that we offer through our Site when you register for a Clearbit account (collectively referred to as the “Services”).

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any website, product or service of any third-party company even if the third-party website links to (or is linked from) our Site. Clearbit does not operate or control those websites, products or services. Please always review the privacy practices of a company before deciding whether to provide any information.

By using our Site or Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.

#### 2\. Information collection and use

Broadly speaking, we collect information in three ways: (1) when you provide it directly to us, (2) when we obtain information about you from third parties or our indexing systems, and (3) passively through technology such as “cookies.” The types of information that we collect and our use of that information are described below.

#### Personal Information

The term “Personal Information”, as used in this Privacy Policy, refers to any information that can be used to identify or relates to an identifiable person. Personal information does not include information that has been aggregated or made anonymous such that it can no longer be reasonably associated with a specific person. Personal Information we collect may include:

  * Names
  * Email addresses
  * Telephone number
  * Credit and debit card number
  * Clearbit account ID and password
  * Social media handle

#### Cookies, Web Server Logs and Other Technologies

Similar to many commercial websites, we utilize “cookies” and other technologies to collect information in connection with our Site. “Cookies” are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a website. Cookies store information accessed through your browser to streamline activities and make the online experience easier and more personalized. Information gathered through cookies and web-server log files may include information such as the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, IP addresses, links to/from any page, and time spent at a site. We use cookie data to measure web traffic and usage activity on our Site for purposes of improving and enhancing the functionality of our Site, to look for possible fraudulent activity, and to better understand the sources of traffic and transactions on our Site. Cookies also allow our servers to remember your account information for future visits and to provide personalized and streamlined information across related pages on our Site. In order to understand and improve the effectiveness of our advertising, we may also use web beacons, cookies, and other technology to identify the fact that you have visited our Site or seen one of our advertisements. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers allow you to automatically decline cookies, or be given the choice of declining or accepting a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site. You may also consider visiting aboutcookies.org, which provides helpful information about cookies. You can choose to disable cookies for our Site but this may limit your ability to use our Site and Services. 

We may use third party advertising networks to serve advertisements that may be of interest to you when you access and use the Site and other websites, based on information relating to your access to and use of the Site and other websites, on any of your devices. To do so, these networks may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through use of web beacons or pixel tags). They may use these technologies, along with information they collect about your online use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile phone and a laptop, and to make decisions about the advertisements you see based on it. If you would like more information about this practice and to learn how to opt out of it in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

Certain information is collected by most browsers, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and version, language, and browser type and version. We use this information to ensure that the Site functions properly.

Your IP address is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. An IP address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses the Site, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We use IP addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels, diagnosing server problems and administering the Services. We may also derive your approximate location from your IP address.

We use third-party analytics services, such as Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site and enhance your experience when you use the Service. For more information on how Google uses this data, go to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You may also download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add on, available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

#### Site Visitors

To simply browse our Site, you are not required to provide any Personal Information. However, we may gather information from cookies and similar technologies, as described directly above, for the purposes of monitoring and improving our Site and understanding and improving the effectiveness of our advertising.

#### Site Users

To gain full access to our Site and Services, you must register for a Clearbit account. When you register for an account, we collect Personal Information such as the following:

  * Your name, company name, location, email address, phone number, and account password, to set up your account

  * Your IP addresses, devices, and locations used to access Clearbit, which will be linked to your account for fraud detection/prevention purposes

#### Clearbit Browser Extensions, Including Connect

Clearbit may offer free browser-based add-ons, extensions or plug-ins (collectively, “Clearbit Browser Extensions”), including Clearbit’s Connect service, which may collect personal and other information. 

When you install Connect, you grant us access to your Gmail or Outlook account and permission to access, use, and share certain information contained therein. This information may include contacts’ names, email addresses, email headers, social media handles, contacts-in-common, business phone numbers, business-related postal addresses, supervisors’ names, assistants’ names, job titles and departments, company names, corporate website URLs, IP addresses and social networking URLs (“Connect Information”). Connect’s technology automatically extracts these types of information from your emails and address book in those accounts.

We use Collect Information collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy, in combination with publicly-available information and data we license from selected third parties, to improve the quality of Connect Information provided to you and others through the Services. By using Connect or otherwise providing Personal Information relating to other people to us, you confirm that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### Clearbit Forms

When you use Clearbit Forms, you grant us permission to access and use the information your website visitors or other individuals submit to you through Clearbit Forms to provide this service to you, and to use this information to enrich and improve the accuracy of company-level data supplied to you and other Clearbit customers through Clearbit services.

#### Children

Our Site and Services are directed to the general public. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13 years of age.

#### Use

We may use Personal Information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy for our legitimate business interests, including to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, complete your transactions, provide you with customer service, send administrative information to you, and to personalize your experience on the Site and Services. We may also use Personal Information and other information collected through the Site or Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site and Services, to better understand our users and to improve the Site and Services. We may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. Information regarding how to opt-out of marketing communications is provided in Section 4 (“Choice and opt-out”) below.

We may use and disclose information that is not Personal Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. In some instances, we may combine non-Personal Information with Personal Information. If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined.

#### 3\. Sharing and disclosure of information

We may disclose your Personal Information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including to third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, auditing and other services.

We may disclose your Personal Information to law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties if we believe necessary or appropriate: (i) to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process, (ii) to comply with laws, statutes, rules or regulations, (iii) to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our Terms of Service.

In addition, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar events, any information in our possession may be transferred to our successor or assign.

#### _Disclosures Through Browser Extensions Like Connect:_

If you are a user of Connect, the Connect Information (including, but not limited to Personal Information) that we collect through your use of Connect may be shared with other users of the Services. However, if you have a Connect Premium membership, we will not share your Connect Information with other users of the Services. Connect will never identify you as the source of any particular Connect Information, except in connection with the disclosures described above.

#### 4\. Choice and opt-out

We may occasionally email you with information about offers or new services. You can opt out of these marketing email communications by replying with unsubscribe in the subject line, or via an unsubscribe link included in such communications. However, you will continue to receive certain email communications related to your account including information regarding transactions and your relationship with Clearbit.

#### 5\. Protection of information

Although no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we take reasonable steps to protect Personal Information. Clearbit maintains reasonable administrative, technical, and physical procedures to protect information stored in our servers, which are located primarily in the United States.

#### 6\. Changes and notifications

This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. We reserve the right, in our sole and absolute discretion, to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically to check for updates. Any changes will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Your use of the Site or Services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.

#### 7\. Jurisdictional disclosures

The Site and Services are controlled and operated by us from the United States and are not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Site and Services you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country. In certain circumstances, courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies or security authorities in those other countries may be entitled to access your Personal Information.

#### 8\. Access to information; Contact us

If you have a Clearbit account, you can update your account information by signing into Clearbit account. You also can update your Personal Information by contacting us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Information in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Site or Services. Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or information practices.

You may contact us as follows: [support@clearbit.com](mailto:support@clearbit.com)

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.
